{
    "id": "31b1e6c2d66d4903b74201114452fb3e",
    "title": "Gap Fills Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I ……………………… sure that they are cheating us.",
            "description": "When feel is used to talk about reactions and opinions, it is not normally used in the continuous form.",
            "answers": [
                "feel",
                "am feeling",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0745d3e5dab74974a0be601c66083304"
        },
        {
            "question": "You are ………………………… an amazing hostess!",
            "description": "In exclamations, we use such before an adjective + plural noun.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "such",
                "very"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "06354440c24f4323be524bc4b68f2723"
        },
        {
            "question": "That was ……………………….. generous of you.",
            "description": "So is used before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "too",
                "so",
                "such"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "60a6b7cf61674dae8b9c7c3e9dc487e3"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………. him to turn up in the afternoon.",
            "description": "Before an indirect object, wait and hope are followed by for.",
            "answers": [
                "expect",
                "wait",
                "hope"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5eaea169078045d980cafef3cfb5f8ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "He was accused of stealing someone ……………………….. ideas.",
            "description": "Else has a possessive form – else’s.",
            "answers": [
                "else",
                "else's"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "0e738e2239614bccafb0463dc612b943"
        },
        {
            "question": "She was ………………………. anxious to sit still.",
            "description": "Too is not used with much before an adjective.",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "too",
                "too much"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "b5d56989c50e4b009728f2e2aa8d605e"
        },
        {
            "question": "I was completely …………………………. after the journey.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "exhausted",
                "exhausting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dfefa9f589a14394b05187ce5d23b57c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have difficulty ……………………………. names and faces.",
            "description": "Difficulty is followed by in + ing form.",
            "answers": [
                "to remember",
                "in remembering"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5695f95f6590409199cebb07b3e1f22d"
        },
        {
            "question": "The whole town was ……………………….. water.",
            "description": "We use under when something is covered by what is over it.",
            "answers": [
                "below",
                "under",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "35732c4d54d34c72bc1eaabd6fc52188"
        },
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like this coat ………………………., it is too expensive.",
            "description": "Besides is similar to also.",
            "answers": [
                "beside",
                "besides",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "335cf966b34a4c4d8b5e1a8e0b955bf8"
        },
        {
            "question": "How do you …………………………. the washing machine?",
            "description": "We make machines start.",
            "answers": [
                "begin",
                "start",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "909b1431699b49c1b40284a1f1eaac36"
        },
        {
            "question": "If my grandfather had been alive, he ……………………….. 90 this year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "will turn",
                "will have turned",
                "would have turned"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "9779014443e64f0b91cb8461da163367"
        }
    ]
}